https://www.thebonuscode.net/cookie-policy/

Bonus CodeHomeCasino Reviews888.comCasino.comCasino RedKingsEUcasinoMansion CasinoMegaCasinoNetBet CasinoPartyCasinoSlotsMagicSlots HeavenWilliam HillCookie PolicyIntroWe believe in being transparent with our users about how we collect and use their data. To find out more about this and us as a data controller, you can read our Privacy Policy.This Cookie Policy is aimed at making it clear for website users (“you”) how, when and why we use cookies.For the information on how to delete or block cookies, please see the section How can I change my cookie settings? below. However, before you take any action with regard to cookies, we warmly advise you to read this policy.Which information can you find in this policy?Our use of cookiesAbout cookiesWhich cookies do we use and what is their purpose?Essential cookies Preference and functionality cookies  Analytics cookies  Marketing cookies Third party cookiesHow can I change my cookie settings?Opt-out from third party service we useChanging browser settingsHow to disable Flash cookiesVariation clauseOur use of cookiesAny browser visiting our Website will receive cookies from us. Insofar as cookies we use are not strictly necessary for the provision of this website, we will ask you to consent to our use of cookies when you first visit our website.We use cookies on our Website because we wish all of our users to have the best possible on-site experience. Information provided via cookies makes it possible to optimise your thebonuscode.net experience.Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies. In our Privacy Policy you can find out more about what personal data relating to our users is being processed.Back to topAbout cookiesCookies are small text files that are placed on your device by websites that you visit. It enables the website to remember your actions and preferences (such as login, language, font size and other display preferences) over a period of time, so you don’t have to keep re-entering them whenever you come back to the site or browse from one page to another. The use of cookies helps you to navigate between pages efficiently, helps remember your preferences and improve your browsing experience in other ways. Cookies can also help ensure that the marketing you see online is more relevant to you and your interests.Other technologies, including data we store on your web browser or device, identifiers associated with your device and other software are used for similar purposes. In this policy, we refer to all of these technologies as “cookies.”Cookies can be classified by their lifespan, the domain to which they belong and place of storage.By lifespan, cookies are either:session cookies which are erased when the user closes the browser – session cookies only last for as long as the session (usually the current visit to a website or a browser session).persistent cookies which remain on the user’s computer/device for a pre-defined period of time (unless deleted by the user before the expiry date). Persistent cookies help us to recognise you, so it’s easier to return to our Website or interact with our service without having to sign in or change your settings every time. After you sign in,As for the domain to which it belongs, there are either:first-party cookies which are set by the web server of the visited page and share the same domain orthird-party cookies stored by a different domain to the visited page’s domain. This can happen when the webpage references a file, such as JavaScript, located outside of its’ domain.Taking into account where cookies are stored, there are:browser cookies that are sent by a website and stored on the user’s browser. Browser cookies store less than Flash cookies and only the browser where the cookies are stored may access them.flash cookies are known as local shared objects and they are different from browser cookies because of the amount, type and manner in which the data is stored. They are stored outside of the browser and they may be accessed by multiple browser on same computer.To find out more about cookies, visit www.aboutcookies.org or www.allaboutcookies.org.Back to topWhich cookies do we use and what is their purpose?We use all types of cookies that are explained above. A detailed description of our cookies, their functions and sources can be found below.Essential cookiesEssential cookies are necessary for our website to work effectively. They help make the website usable by enabling basic functionalities like page navigation and access to secure areas of the website. This type of cookies may be used to protect and accelerate our website by automatically optimising the delivery of our content. This is how you get the fastest page load times and best performance. Also, essential cookies may be used for security reasons and to identify our trusted visitors. They may filter bots and distinguish them from legitimate users, preventing any form of spam activity on our website.These cookies do not correspond to any user ID in our web application, nor do the cookies store any personally identifiable information. We advise you not to switch off these cookies. If you set your browser to block or alert you about these cookies, please be aware that after doing so, some parts of the webpage may not work.Preference and functionality cookiesPreference cookies enable a website to remember information that changes the way the website behaves or looks, like your preferred language or the region that you are in. They may also be used to provide services you have asked for such as watching a video, commenting on a blog or using a live chat service.Analytics cookiesAnalytics cookies help website owners to understand how visitors interact with websites by collecting and reporting information anonymously. We use different analytics cookies in order to analyse information about how our website is being used. Analytics cookies can process information about the number of visitors to the website, where visitors to the website came from, the pages they visit, scrolling activities, downloads, information about user agent, time spent on the website and approximate geo-location of a device that you use to access our website. We use this information to compile reports that help us to improve the website. Reports may be visually presented through heat maps and anonymised screen recordings. All data we process by use of this type of cookies are presented in an aggregated form and/or pseudonymised.We mainly use analytics cookies provided by Google Analytics, Clicky, Hotjar, Visual Website Optimizer. However, please be aware that we may use analytics cookies provided by other companies which services we may also use for analytics and analytical purposes.Marketing cookiesMarketing cookies are used to track visitors across websites. The intention is to display advertisements that are relevant and engaging for the individual user.For marketing purposes we may use various services including, but not limited to, Eloqua, and AdForm. For the purpose of regular functioning of marketing services, marketing cookies are used. These cookies serve to personalise the way we communicate with you. If you accept to receive advertising material, marketing cookies help us to evaluate your personal preferences toward specific content that we further use to deliver advertising material to you that correspond to your preferences.Please be aware that we may use marketing cookies provided by other companies whose services we may use for marketing purposes. Also, third party cookies (see the section below) may be placed by our partners in order to promote their products. Promotional activities may include inter alia providing interstitial advertisement.Third party cookiesThird parties may set cookies when you visit our Website. Sometimes that is because we have hired the third party to provide services on our behalf. In other cases, it is because our web pages contain advertisements from third parties, or content such as videos and news. Because your browser connects to those third parties’ web servers to retrieve that content, third parties are able to set or read their own cookies on your device and may collect information about your online activities across websites or online services. Finally, in some cases third party tracking cookies may also be necessary for the effective use of affiliate links and the performance of any affiliate agreements we have in place.Back to topHow can I change my cookie settings?You may at any time choose to disable some or all of the cookies. You have several ways to do disable cookies.Opt-out from third party service we useYou can opt-out from being tracked by some of the third party service providers we mainly rely on, by the following instructions they provide:Google Analytics opt-outClicky opt-outHotJar opt-outVWO opt-outEloqua opt-outAdForm opt-outChanging browser settingsThe most used web browsers allow you to manage the majority of cookies through the browser’s settings. Keep in mind that if you limit the ability of websites to set cookies, you may worsen your overall user experience, since it (inter alia) will no longer be personalised to you.If you still do not want to receive cookies from our Website, you can change your browser settings on a device you are using to access our services. Below you can find short instructions on how to disable cookies on the most popular Internet browsers. Also, you can find links to the cookie management section for the most popular Internet browsers. Please carefully read the following instructions:Internet Explorer: Click on the Tools button, then on Internet Options. In the General tab, choose Browsing history, click on Settings. Then click Select files and select the Cookie(s) you wish to disable. Then close the window containing the list of Cookies and click twice on OK to return to internet. More instructions available here.Firefox browser: Click on the Firefox Menu icon, then on the Tools button, then Options; in the window that appears, select Privacy and collect Remove Specific Cookies. Select the Cookies you wish to disable then remove them. More instructions available here.Safari: click on the Settings button, then on Preferences. In the window that appears, choose Privacy/Security and click on Show Cookies. Select the Cookies you wish to disable then click on Delete or Delete All. More instructions available here.Chrome: click on the Google Chrome menu, then Settings. At the bottom of the page, click on Advanced Settings. In the Privacy section, click on Content Settings. To disable cookies:Select Block sites from storing any data;Click on Cookies and site data then move the mouse over the website which created the Cookie, and click on X in the right corner, or click on Remove All.More information available here.Safari (mobile) – For more information please visit the following link.For instructions on how to disable cookies on Internet browsers that are not given above, please consult the documentation that your browser manufacturer provides.How to disable Flash cookiesChanging browser settings will not remove Flash cookies. If you would like to disable Flash cookies, you can get the instructions here. If you disable Flash cookies, you will not have access to many features that make your experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.Back to topVariation clauseIt may be necessary to amend this Cookie Policy at times based on changing technical and business needs or to comply with legislative or regulatory requirements of EU Data Protection Law.Essential modifications are those that affect your rights and state with regard to the protection and processing of your personal data. The essential modifications may include, but are not limited to, launch of new services, deployment of new technologies and processing your data for new purposes. Therefore, if we make essential modifications to this Cookie Policy, we will send you notice through our Services, or by other means, and give you the opportunity to review the changes before they become effective. You will be asked to consent to the processing of your personal data in accordance with the updated Policy. If you do not consent to this, you may not be able to use your account and services available for registered users.In addition, from time to time we may make minor modifications to our Cookie Policy. These types of modifications may include, but are not limited to, organisational and grammatical changes in order to make this policy easier to read. The fact that you continue to use our services after we publish the updated Cookie Policy with only minor modifications means that the processing of your personal data is subject to the updated Cookie Policy with only minor modifications.We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on cookie use.Back to topRead more: Cookie Policy | Privacy Policy
18+ | Commercial Content | Wagering and T&C's Apply | Play Responsibly
thebonuscode.net uses cookies to give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we will assume that you are happy with it.OkRead more
